[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1985 movie contains this quote: Whos going to believe a talking head? Get a job in a sideshow.?", "correct_answer": "Re-Animator", "incorrect_answers": ["Cannibal Holocaust", "Motel Hell", "Basket Case"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name of the Eudyptes schlegeli penguin species that have a white face and live in the waters surrounding Antarctica?", "correct_answer": "Royal Penguin", "incorrect_answers": ["King Penguin", "All of these", "Emperor Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Starfish are fast moving creatures.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first American city to fluoridate its water system?", "correct_answer": "Grand Rapids, Michigan", "incorrect_answers": ["San Miguel, California", "Yonkers, New York", "Colorado Springs, Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many sailors have seen the Flying Dutchman, a ship doomed to roam the seas forever. Where did the Flying Dutchman reportedly disappear?", "correct_answer": "Cape of Good Hope", "incorrect_answers": ["The East Indies", "The North Sea", "The Atlantic Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What classification of the hands do modern palmists most often use to define the personality of the owner?", "correct_answer": "By elements", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "By seasons", "By animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the President of the United States at the time when Apollo 11 landed on the Moon?", "correct_answer": "Richard Nixon", "incorrect_answers": ["John F. Kennedy", "Lyndon B. Johnson", "Gerald Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film has the following plot?\nLester Burnham is having a midlife crisis and decides to re-evaluate his life, after becoming infatuated with one of his daughters friends.", "correct_answer": "American Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Virgin Suicides", "Dead Poets Society", "Splendor in the Grass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This musical comedy, directed by Nancy Walker, is a pseudo autobiography of 1970s disco group, Village People.", "correct_answer": "Cant Stop the Music", "incorrect_answers": ["The Peoples Singers", "Freddie and His Friends", "Join the Action"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Bandar Seri Begawan?", "correct_answer": "The capital city of an Asian nation", "incorrect_answers": ["The largest city in the Kurdish section of Iraq", "The name of the Prime Minister of a North African nation", "The name of a terrorist organization in Afghanistan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The green color is considered to be the traditional and most sacred color of this religion.", "correct_answer": "Islam", "incorrect_answers": ["Roman Catholicism", "Buddhism", "Hinduism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The capital of this island country is Kingston.", "correct_answer": "Jamaica", "incorrect_answers": ["Haiti", "Hispaniola", "Cuba"]}]